<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Halloween Horror Hacking Hell</title>
    <link>https://halloween-horror-hacking-hell.github.io/Docs/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Halloween Horror Hacking Hell</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 19:39:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://halloween-horror-hacking-hell.github.io/Docs/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Invite</title>
      <link>https://halloween-horror-hacking-hell.github.io/Docs/posts/invite/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 19:39:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halloween-horror-hacking-hell.github.io/Docs/posts/invite/</guid>
      <description>Invite - Halloween Horror Hacking Hell Hello! If you&amp;rsquo;ve received this invite, you were officially invited to the Halloween Horror Hacking Hell (H4). You&amp;rsquo;re not yet aware of it? No problem! Read on and we&amp;rsquo;ll explain everything!
TL;DR: Throw a hackathon, quiz games, and some funky beats into a blender and you&amp;rsquo;ll may receive a big jug of H4.
Simple Hard Facts When: 5th of November 2022 Begin: 3 pm CET (See the schedule for details) Where: Either physically on location or in provided digital space.</description>
      <content>&lt;h1 id=&#34;invite---halloween-horror-hacking-hell&#34;&gt;Invite - Halloween Horror Hacking Hell&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hello! If you&amp;rsquo;ve received this invite, you were officially invited to the Halloween Horror Hacking Hell (H4). You&amp;rsquo;re not yet aware of it? No problem! Read on and we&amp;rsquo;ll explain everything!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TL;DR: Throw a hackathon, quiz games, and some funky beats into a blender and you&amp;rsquo;ll may receive a big jug of H4.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;simple-hard-facts&#34;&gt;Simple Hard Facts&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When: 5th of November 2022&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Begin: 3 pm CET (See the schedule for details)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Where: Either physically on location or in provided digital space.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;schedule&#34;&gt;Schedule&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All of the following times are in CET.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;03:00pm - Arrival &amp;amp; Setup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hackaton
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;03:30pm - Hackaton Introduction&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;03:40pm - Start Hacking&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;07:00pm - Hackaton Deadline&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dinnertime
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;07:00pm - Dinner&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Music &amp;amp; Chillout
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;08:00pm - Chill Bytes [Music]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;08:30pm - Nerdy Jeopardy [Games]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;09:30pm - Retro Future [Music]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;10:00pm - Um, Actually&amp;hellip; [Games]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;11:00pm - Hackaton Voting Closes [Orga]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;11:00pm - Nerds Try To Dance [Music]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;loctions&#34;&gt;Loctions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re providing two different ways to attend the event. You can either join physically or digitally. Both spaces will be connected with a video stream. Read on to figure out how to participate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;join-physically-on-location&#34;&gt;Join Physically On Location&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The physical location will be in Sustrum Moor at &lt;a href=&#34;lenny.farm&#34;&gt;lenny.farm&lt;/a&gt;. Click &lt;a href=&#34;https://goo.gl/maps/5VRgaEzkyajWLxW56&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; for detailed information on how to get there &lt;strong&gt;Important&lt;/strong&gt; If you&amp;rsquo;re planning to attend physically, we need you to sign up so we know how many people to expect. If you want to be there but your schedule doesn&amp;rsquo;t allow for you to be there in the afternoon, you can of course join us later. Just let us know in the signup form as well as any food intolerances. We&amp;rsquo;re going to close the &lt;a href=&#34;https://forms.gle/SjC5aMMaB4BdKDd97&#34;&gt;Signup Form&lt;/a&gt; on the 20th of October at 11:59 pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A couple of notes:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Food and drinks aren&amp;rsquo;t free and we don&amp;rsquo;t want anyone to stay hungry. Please help us out by sending 5€ to the following PayPal account and adding &lt;code&gt;Halloween Horror Hacking Hell&lt;/code&gt; as a message: &lt;a href=&#34;https://paypal.me/tobiasboyer&#34;&gt;https://paypal.me/tobiasboyer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The main location will be a barn. Please make sure to bring a jacket as it might get cold in the evening.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ll provide a WLAN connection and ports on one of our switches. If you want a LAN connection, bring a sufficiently long LAN cable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Please, especially if you&amp;rsquo;re bringing multiple devices, that require an outlet, bring a (safe!!) extension cable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We might be able to organize a place for you to stay overnight. Please create an issue, so we can discuss the details. (See help section for more details on issues)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;join-our-virtual-space&#34;&gt;Join Our Virtual Space&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our virtual space will be open for anyone no binding sign up needed (the size of the virtual location is limited. If we&amp;rsquo;re somehow above the limit, we&amp;rsquo;ll provide access on a first come first serve bases but will prioritize people who signed up). All games and music will be streamed into the space. We&amp;rsquo;ll be using &amp;ldquo;VRChat&amp;rdquo; as a meetup space. Click &lt;a href=&#34;https://youtu.be/WtENuEbqUXk&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; for a guide on how to use the software. Hint: VRChat is freely available via Steam and can be used with a VR Headset and without.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Here will be a link to the virtual space&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can of course choose an avatar, that makes you happy. There are just a couple of rules:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No avatars that are rated poor or worse&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No avatars that are offensive or not safe for work in any form&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nothing that would be against the VRChat terms of service&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;signups&#34;&gt;Signups&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Click here to sign up: &lt;a href=&#34;https://forms.gle/SjC5aMMaB4BdKDd97&#34;&gt;Signup Form&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;hackaton&#34;&gt;Hackaton&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The goal of the hackaton is to show how beautiful coding can be, by coding a visual animation in a limited environment with limited tools.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This results in the following constraints:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The result can be anything that fits with the theme (which will be announced on the day)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The result has to be written in &lt;a href=&#34;https://p5js.org/&#34;&gt;P5.js&lt;/a&gt; and has to run on a Raspberry Pi 3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The result will be presented for 5min on a big screen&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The result should be rendered in 1920 by 1080 pixels&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The result won&amp;rsquo;t have access to any audio&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The result can&amp;rsquo;t use any external scripts or graphics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There will be a couple of technical rules about how to name files and alike but those will be announced in the future as well as how to&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the end, every attendee can vote and the winner will take home a cool price.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;music&#34;&gt;Music&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The music will follow the aforementioned themes, but those themes are quite flexible. Want to hear your favorite song? Submit it to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://open.spotify.com/playlist/4CohnYSDKokoqwem9O3Ylm?si=037212fba16649fd&amp;amp;pt=f18844e47c384f0a19353a0068ee58fe&#34;&gt;Spotify playlist&lt;/a&gt; and we&amp;rsquo;ll make sure to find a nice place for it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;help&#34;&gt;Help&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Don&amp;rsquo;t know how to do draw that really cute cat in P5.js? Do you have a nasty bug and need second pair of eyes? You can use the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/Halloween-Horror-Hacking-Hell/Hellish-Contributions/discussions&#34;&gt;discussion section on Github&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In case you have any question, problem, or something that should be brought to our attention, we&amp;rsquo;ll urge you to create an &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/Halloween-Horror-Hacking-Hell/Hellish-Contributions/issues&#34;&gt;issue on Github&lt;/a&gt; (before the event as well as during the event). This helps us to keep everything organized and make the event an awesome experience for everyone. In case something goes wrong, please provide as many details as you can.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;blinky-lights&#34;&gt;Blinky Lights&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wanna bring some? Please do! Let&amp;rsquo;s drown in rainbow vomit!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
